fcall.in 2016-04-01

# Free Call | Free Recharge | Free Online Recharge | Free Mobile Recharge Website | Free Calling - Fcallz.com

fcallz takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by fcallz you agree to the collection and use of your data by fcallz in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

if you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact fcallz Customer Support Desk at 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This Privacy Policy covers **fcallz** treatment of personally identifiable information that fcallz collects when you are on the site, and when you use services provided by fcallz. This policy also covers fcallz's treatment of any personally identifiable information that fcallz's business partners share with fcallz .

**What information is or may be collected from you**

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies" sent to your browser from: 

  * an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use 
  * Source and destination number to which you are making call 
  * What sms or call conversation made (if any complaint got by as against you)

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: 

  * name including first and last name and preferably middle name.
  * email address and ip address.
  * mobile phone number and contact details .

**How is this information used**

We use your email address to send you: 

  * Password reminder and registration confirmation 
  * Changes in the service's policy or terms of use 

Note: We send users newsletters and updates upon registration. We send newsletters and/or promotional emails on behalf of our alliance partners. 

We use may your Mobile number to send you:

  * Password reminder and Registration confirmation
  * Special feature updates
  * Event based services such as renewal notices, invites, email alerts , reminders etc.,
  * Promotional SMSes on behalf of our alliance partners

We use your personal information to: 

  * help us provide personalized features 
  * to get in touch with you in the case of password retrieval and policy changes 
  * to provide the services requested by you 
  * to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy 

We use contact information internally to: 

  * direct our efforts for product improvement 
  * contact you as a survey respondent 
  * notify you if you win any contest; and 
  * send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers 

Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to: 

  * remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective; 
  * recognize your access privileges to our Web sites 
  * track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player's progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings 
  * make sure that you don't see the same ad repeatedly 
  * help diagnose problems with our server 
  * administer our Web sites 
  * track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites 

**Information Sharing And disclosure**

We do not share or rent your email addresses or Mobile number with third parties except our alliance partners.

fcallz will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information; 
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
  * We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues. 
  * We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer; 
  * We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable and email address information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Refunds**

If recharge fails then we will try to recharge again and if you do not get recharge within 48 hours of   
attempting recharge you cna contact us directly at [admin@fcallz.com](mailto:shaikhsahfique98@gmail.com) with all details.  
We will recharge your mobile again with in 24 hours.
